if your diet and training are on point
first then a fat burner may help to
speed up and optimize your efforts but
like it won't do the work for you but
they can provide a little extra boost
which is worthwhile to a lot of people
the pack of ingredients that could
potentially coax calorie burn and a
quality fat burner might help you move
along those last few pounds of fat so in
this video today we've collected the
best fat burners for men if you want to
see the full written version of this
video by the way you can just google it
with bar band plus best men's fat
burners and if you want to buy any of
these just by any chance you can just
click on the links in the description
below one more thing before we get into
the list i should make it clear that i'm
not a doctor and this is not medical
advice make sure you speak to your
physician before you start any new
supplement or training regimen the best
men's fat burner overall is jack
factory's burn xt contains all your big
header fat burning ingredients like
l-carnitine that might help you to turn
fat into energy there's a green tea leaf
extract that can help with weight loss
and blood sugar potentially plenty of
caffeine that can help to like boost and
burn energy levels a cayenne pepper
fruit extract that can help to up your
metabolism increase thermogenesis
there's also even some black pepper
extract which is meant to help you to
absorb everything here more effectively
there are no fillers or dyes or anything
in these capsules and you can take one
or two pills at once just make sure you
take them with some food to avoid any
potential digestive issues next up is
the best fat burner for belly fat it is
fan gold while fen gold includes all of
the major fat burning ingredients you're
likely to find it also throws in some
extra ingredients to potentially help
you have a better workout so like most
type burners it contains cayenne pepper
caffeine green tea but unlike a lot of
other fat burners it also has some
ingredients for potential ergogenic
benefits so that would include like
rhodiola sp which can help to combat
workout fatigue and improve focus you
can potentially work harder and longer
in the gym it also contains an
l-theanine which might help to increase
thermogenesis and also focus it's a
really cool supplement feng gold also
has tyrosine which also has links to
improve focus so like you know giving
you some more time to hone in your
resistance training at the gym that kind
of thing plus this park is soy free
lactose free gmo free and vegan the
label is also really transparent with
all the ingredients listed and the
amounts as well there's a lot of
proprietary blends out there where they
just have ingredients that have like
interesting resource support in their
usage but not the doses fan gold has
ingredients and it has the doses and
it's probably good for a workout as well
so yeah big fan of thin gold next up for
the most thermogenic fat burner is
transparent labs it's got a big dose of
cayenne pepper right which contains
capsaicinoids which is the ingredient
that makes the peppers spicy but some
research suggests it could also
potentially help with weight loss
through increased thermogenesis and
that's not the only useful ingredient in
this product transparent labs is fat
burner also contains
forsyline which can help to promote the
release of fatty acids from fat tissue
and there's also green tea and 5ht which
both may help to increase them genesis
as well in addition you'll have like
mood focus and energy boosting
ingredients in this like tyrosine fenin
and caffeine and 5htp could help to
increase focus as well and transparent
labs encourages you to take two of these
capsules twice daily which might seem
like a lot but you know there are fat
burners with more pills to take than
that and in any event if you do find it
to be a lot of pills this is unless a
very very effective product and you know
probably worth it next up is the best
natural fat burner it is legion's
phoenix stem free fat burner they've got
two phoenix's there's like the stem free
and then the regular one took the
stem-free one here today contains no
artificial sweeteners or food dyes or
unwanted like fillings or anything it's
very natural fat burning blend we also
really like that legion has a really
good record of transparency like talking
about the exact doses of all the
ingredients all that kind of stuff and
it's really they really focus a lot on
like the dosing and the quality of the
ingredients there's a lot of studies all
over the website and the product page in
the description below the ingredients
here include thai ginseng and 5 htp and
caroluma fimbriata and forskolin which
all could potentially help to burn fat
suppress appetite and regulate your
metabolism plus legion has included an
added dose of b vitamins which can
potentially help with focus and maintain
energy levels when you are consuming
like the recommended daily intake of
these nutrients next up is the best fat
burner powder stacked factories burnt xd
thermogenic fat burner powder if you
prefer a powder over a pill
jack factory has a box of 15 sticks of
powdered fat burning here benefit of a
powder supplement is that your body
doesn't have to digest like the capsule
you get in the pills you drink it mixed
with water which allows your blood to
absorb it more quickly the product only
contains five main ingredients we've got
l-carnitine green tea extract caffeine
red pepper fruit extract and black
pepper extract but these hit all the
major fat burning ingredients plus it
comes in three tasty flavors you got
blackberry lemonade pineapple punch and
watermelon lime the only potential
downside here is that these flavorings
are made with artificial flavors and
sweetness so if you're steering clear of
those you might want to stay clear of
this product but if that doesn't bother
you it's pretty tasty way to get your
fat burning powder next up is the best
pre-workout fat burner so as we've
mentioned there are a lot of fat burners
out there that contain caffeine which
have some links to increase like fat
oxidation and metabolism that sort of
thing but our favorite pre-workout fat
burner is marketed more as a pre-workout
than a fat burner but it is in fact a
pre-workout that contains a lot of fat
burning ingredients it is
transparent labs
lean so this re-workout does contain all
your typical pre-workout ingredients
like citrulline malate beta-alanine
betaine branched-chain amino acids it
also contains l-carnitine which could
help to turn fat into usable energy and
caffeine which although great for energy
i've mentioned has been linked to fat
burn transplant labs lean also contains
not official sweeteners or colorings or
preservatives and it's also gluten-free
and non-gmo so this supplement comes in
six flavors and they're all again all
natural no artificial flavor sweetness
or anything like that if what you prefer
is a very easily transportable pill or
like bunch of pills you could take with
you wherever you go this isn't the
product for you but if you want a very
tasty product that's great to take
pre-workout and here's a whole bunch of
ergogenic aids
transparent labs lean i like it a lot
next up is the best fat burner for
bodybuilding it is burn lab pro the only
product on this list that contains hmb
hydroxy methyl butyrate which is a
metabolite that has been linked to
increased lean body mass opting for a
fat burn with hmb may help men to retain
and maybe even build muscle and perform
well in the gym
even if you're trimming down your
waistline this product is also
stimulant-free and it contains
ingredients like forsyline and cayenne
pepper extracts for thermogenesis and
potential fat burn it's black pepper
extract could also help with the
absorption of all the products
ingredients burn lamb pro is in addition
vegan so if you haven't be vegan
bodybuilder you'll be happy with this
one too next up is the most affordable
fat burner the best fat burner for the
money
jack factory burn x t it places a big
emphasis on thermogenic ingredients they
could like technically raise the body's
internal temperature for some extra
calorie burns so it bursts there's five
ingredients there's acetyl-l carnitine
green tea leaf extract caffeine capsule
max and black pepper fruit extract so
it's like more affordable doesn't have a
huge range of ingredients but it's still
very effective for getting high quality
potentially fat burning ingredients this
product skips out on extras like
tyrosine or hmb that some other more
expensive fat burners include
except for the best premium men's fat
burner it is fen gold we're really
impressed with the ingredients here
contains capsimax black pepper caffeine
and niacin to help with thermogenesis or
like temperature-induced calorie burn
there's chromium picolinate which may
help to ease anxiety maybe and decrease
appetite fungal also includes extras
like tyrosine that could help you focus
and helps make your workouts more
productive it's also 100 natural soy
free lactose free gmo free and vegan and
all the ingredients and their amounts
are very transparently listed clearly on
the label unlike some of their cheaper
competitors with this level of quality
it is at a higher price tag compared to
other picks on this list but if you're
willing to pay for the best check out
feng gold all right that about does it
for our best men's fat burners video
remember if you want to see a written
version of all this you can go through
it at your own pace just google barbin
plus best men's fat burners we got a
bunch of like scientific references in
there as well if you want to check those
out uh if you're gonna buy these make
sure you click on the links in the
description below that will take you
right there and lastly make sure you
subscribe here to barbara's youtube
channel because we've got a whole lot
more reviews and also news and like
interviews and exercise guides and other
sorts of stuff around the world of sync
sports
[Music]